(Bill Murray(on screen):)on ESP ability.
(Raj:)Huh.
(Raj:)Bill Murray did get it wrong.
(Howard:)Jump ahead to the Stay Puft
Marshmallow Man.
No!
(Sheldon stammers)
(Howard:)Leonard's right.
(Sheldon:)We can't just jump ahead.
(Sheldon:)We have to watch
the whole movie.
Look.
(Leonard:)We keep procrastinating.
We saw Back to the Future II,
(Leonard:)pigeons playing
ping-pong,
(Leonard:)a bunch of countries
that look like genitals
(Leonard:)and one guy whose genitals
look like Denmark!
(Raj:)Yeah, sorry for
clicking on that.
(Leonard:)It's late.
We've wasted hours.
(Leonard:)Can we please find it
in ourselves
(Leonard:)to do any amount of work
tonight?
(Sheldon:)But we didn't see them bust
one ghost.
So y-you're saying
we should stand here
(Leonard:)in my lab on a
Saturday night
(Leonard:)and watch the rest
of Ghostbusters
(Leonard:)on a crappy laptop?
(Howard:)No.
♪ ♪